Finding Aid for Detroit News records.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Scrapbooks
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 7 C, 1954-1974 (Box 134)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 8 C-E, 1954-1976 (Box 134)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 9 E-F, 1952-1977 (Box 135)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 10 F-G, 1953-1974 (Box 135)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 11 G-H, 1952-1979 (Box 135)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 12 H-I, 1969-1981 (Box 135)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 13 I, 1974 (Box 136)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 14 I-K, 1953-1980 (Box 136)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 15 L-M, 1958-1981 (Box 136)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 16 M, 1969-1974 (Box 136)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 17 M-N, 1954-1976 (Box 136)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 18 N, 1954-1977 (Box 137)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 19 N-O, 1959-1975 (Box 137)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 20 P, 1955-1976 (Box 137)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 21 P, 1961-1978 (Box 137)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 22 P, 1952-1974 (Box 137)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 23 P, 1960-1972 (Box 138)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 24 P, 1959-1976 (Box 138)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 25 P, 1955-1972 (Box 138)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 26 P, 1967-1975 (Box 138)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 27 P-R, 1952-1976 (Box 138)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 28 R, 1957-19781 (Box 139)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 29 R-S, 1959-1974 (Box 139)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 30 S, 1956-1978 (Box 139)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 31 S-T, 1952-1982 (Box 139)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 32 T, 1957-1980 (Box 139)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 33 T, 1957-1982 (Box 140)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 34 U-T, 1952-1981 (Box 140)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 35 V, 1962-1970 (Box 140)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 36 V, 1971-1978 (Box 140)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 37 V-W, 1953-1974 (Box 140)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 38 W, 1973 (Box 141)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 39 W, 1973-1974 (Box 141)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 40 W, 1974-1982 (Box 141)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 41 W, 1960-1974 (Box 141)
  - Nixon, Richard M.-President-Book 42 W-Z and Miscellaneous, 1968-1982 (Box 141)
  - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy-Book 1 A-K, 1955-1978 (Box 142)
  - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy-Book 2 L-Z and Miscellaneous, 1960-1982 (Box 142)
  - Organizations-American-Legion-Convention-Detroit, 1931-1961 (Box 142)
  - Organizations-Black-Black Legion-Book 1, 1936-1937 (Box 142)
  - Organizations-Black-Black Legion-Book 2, 1936-1968 (Box 142)
  - Organizations-Ku Klux Klan-Book 1 A-I, 1921-1980 (Box 142)
  - Organizations-Ku Klux Klan-Book 2 I-O, 1922-1980 (Box 143)
  - Organizations-Ku Klux Klan-Book 3 P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1922-1982 (Box 143)
  - Organizations-Newsboys-Old Newsboys-Detroit-Book 1, 1917-1980 (Box 143)
  - Organizations-Newsboys-Old Newsboys-Detroit-Book 2, 1930-1946 (Box 143)
  - Organizations-Newsboys-Old Newsboys-Detroit-Book 3, 1946-1961 (Box 143)
  - Organizations-Newsboys-Old Newsboys-Detroit Book 4, 1961-1982 (Box 144)
  - Organizations-United Foundation-Detroit-Campaign-Book 1, 1949-1982 (Box 144)
  - Organizations-United Foundation-Detroit-Campaign-Book 2, 1960-1982 (Box 144)
  - Osborn, Chase Salmon-Governor-Book 1, 1895-1918 (Box 144)
  - Osborn, Chase Salmon-Governor-Book 2, 1914-1949 (Box 144)
  - Oswald, Lee Harvey.-Assassin-A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1963-1981 (Box 144)
  - Peron, Juan D.-Argentina Politician-A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1947-1976 (Box 145)
  - Piggins, Edward S.-Judge-Book 1-A-M, 1928-1969 (Box 145)
  - Piggins, Edward S.-Judge-Book 2-N-Z and Miscellaneous, 1954-1972 (Box 145)
  - Pingree, Hazen S.-Biography by Cyril & Marjorie Player, 1932 (Box 145)
  - Potter, Charles E.-Politician, 1949-1964 (Box 145)
  - Prohibition-Book 1, 1919-1953 (Box 145)
  - Prohibition-Book 2, 1921-1966 (Box 146)
  - Prohibition-Book 3, 1918-1951 (Box 146)
  - Prohibition-Book 4, 1916-1936 (Box 146)
  - Prohibition-Book 5, 1919-1968 (Box 146)
  - Prohibition-Book 6, 1918-1976 (Box 146)
  - Prohibition-Series, 1923-1930 (Box 146)
  - Race Riots-Detroit-Miscellaneous, 1967-1990 (Box 147)
  - Reading, Richard W.-Former Detroit Mayor, 1924-1963 (Box 147)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 1 A, 1967-1985 (Box 147)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 2 A, 1981-1985 (Box 147)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 3 B, 1966-1984 (Box 148)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 4 B, 1981-1985 (Box 148)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 5 B-C, 1980-1985 (Box 148)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 6 C, 1981-1984 (Box 148)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 7 D, 1968-1985 (Box 148)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 8 E, 1974-1985 (Box 149)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 9 F, 1974-1985 (Box 149)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 10 G-H, 1965-1985 (Box 149)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 11 I-K, 1980-1985 (Box 149)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 12 L-M, 1980-1984 (Box 149)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 13 M, 1981-1985 (Box 150)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 14 N, 1976-1985 (Box 150)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 15 N-P, 1968-1985 (Box 150)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 16 P, 1976-1985 (Box 150)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 17 P, 1967-1985 (Box 151)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 18 P-Q, 1964-1985 (Box 151)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 19 R, 1965-1985 (Box 151)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 20 S, 1969-1985 (Box 151)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 21 T, 1966-1985 (Box 152)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 22 T, 1963-1985 (Box 152)
  - Reagan, Ronald-Book 23 U-Z and Miscellaneous, 1967-1985 (Box 152)
  - Republicans-Convention-National-Book 1, 1856-1933 (Box 152)
  - Republicans-Convention-National-Book 2, 1935-1948 (Box 152)
  - Republicans-Convention-National-Book 3, 1951-1960 (Box 153)
  - Republicans-Convention-National-Book 4, 1962-1978 (Box 153)
  - Republicans-Convention-National-Book 5, 1977-1980 (Box 153)
  - Republicans-Convention-National-Book 6, 1979-1982 (Box 153)
  - Republicans-Convention-National-Book 7, 1983-1988 (Box 153)
  - Reuther, Walter-Labor Leader-Book 1 A-B, 1940-1971 (Box 154)
  - Reuther, Walter-Labor Leader-Book 2 C-H, 1939-1970 (Box 154)
  - Reuther, Walter-Labor Leader-Book 3 I-R, 1940-1968 (Box 154)
  - Reuther, Walter-Labor Leader-Book 4 S-U, 1939-1970 (Box 154)
  - Reuther, Walter-Labor Leader-Book 5 V-Z and Miscellaneous, 1942-1970 (Box 154)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.-Politician-Book 1 A-K, 1930-1977 (Box 155)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.-Politician-Book 2 L-P, 1930-1974 (Box 155)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.-Politician-Book 3 P-S, 1960-1976 (Box 155)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.-Politician-Book 4 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1959-1976 (Box 155)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 1 A, 1945-1976 (Box 155)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 2 B, 1943-1968 (Box 156)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 3 C-D, 1960-1976 (Box 156)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 4 E-G, 1944-1969 (Box 156)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 5 G, 1962-1966 (Box 156)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 6 G-K, 1959-1973 (Box 156)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 7 L-M, 1942-1968 (Box 157)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 8 M-P, 1961-1969 (Box 157)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 9 P, 1942-1977 (Box 157)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 10 P-S, 1957-1971 (Box 157)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 11 S-T, 1959-1971 (Box 158)
  - Romney, George-Michigan Politician-Book 12 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1961-1982 (Box 158)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 1 A, 1933-1945 (Box 158)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 2 A-B, 1929-1982 (Box 158)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 3 B, 1928-1971 (Box 159)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 4 C, 1933-1954 (Box 159)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 5 C-E, 1929-1980 (Box 159)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 6 E-F, 1925-1982 (Box 159)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 7 F-I, 1931-1976 (Box 160)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 8 I-M, 1931-1982 (Box 160)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 9 M, 1933-1945 (Box 160)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 10 M-O, 1933-1943 (Box 160)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 11 P, 1930-1952 (Box 160)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 12 P, 1931-1944 (Box 161)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 13 P, 1932-1944 (Box 161)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 14 P-S, 1928-1945 (Box 161)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 15 S, 1932-1945 (Box 161)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 16 S-T, 1932-1946 (Box 161)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 17 T-W, 1932-1945 (Box 162)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 18 W, 1932-1946 (Box 162)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.-President-Book 19 W-Z and Miscellaneous, 1931-1977 (Box 162)
  - Roosevelt, Mrs. Franklin D.-Wife of President-Book 1 A-K, 1933-1976 (Box 162)
  - Roosevelt, Mrs. Franklin D.-Wife of President-Book 2 L-T, 1928-1982 (Box 162)
  - Roosevelt, Mrs. Franklin D.-Wife of President-Book 3 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1933-1982 (Box 162)
  - Ruby, Jack-Murderer, 1963-1979 (Box 163)
  - Rusk, Dean-Book 1 A-M, 1949-1969 (Box 163)
  - Rusk, Dean-Book 2 N-Z and Miscellaneous, 1959-1977 (Box 163)
  - Scranton, William W.-Politician-A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1962-1974 (Box 163)
  - Sheppard, Dr. Samuel-Murderer-Book 1 A-T, 1954-1970 (Box 163)
  - Sheppard, Dr. Samuel-Murderer-Book 2 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1954-1975 (Box 163)
  - Sigler, Kim-Michigan Governor-Book 1 A-G, 1943-1950 (Box 164)
  - Sigler, Kim-Michigan Governor-Book 2 G-Z and Miscellaneous, 1945-1982 (Box 164)
  - Smith, Alfred E.-New York City-Book 1, 1920-1935 (Box 164)
  - Smith, Alfred E.-New York City-Book 2, 1928 (Box 164)
  - Smith, Alfred E.-New York City-Book 3, 1928-1958 (Box 164)
  - Smith, John W.-Book 1, 1914-1942 (Box 164)
  - Smith, John W.-Book 2, 1925-1942 (Box 165)
  - Smith, John W.-Book 3, 1924-1937 (Box 165)
  - Smith, John W.-Book 4, 1924-1974 (Box 165)
  - Soap Box Derby-Detroit-Book 1, 1934-1959 (Box 165)
  - Soap Box Derby-Detroit-Book 2, 1959-1982 (Box 165)
  - Spelling Bee-Detroit News, 1941-1982 (Box 165)
  - Staebler, Neil-Politician, 1952-1979 (Box 166)
  - Stalin, Josef-Russian Politician-Book 1 A-P, 1929-1978 (Box 166)
  - Stalin, Josef-Russian Politician-Book 2 R-Z and Miscellaneous, 1926-1978 (Box 166)
  - Studebaker, 1923-1983 (Box 166)
  - Surgery-Heart, 1923-1982 (Box 166)
  - Swainson, John B.-Michigan Governer-Judge-Book 1 A-G, 1959-1980 (Box 167)
  - Swainson, John B.-Michigan Governer-Judge-Book 2 G-J, 1959-1962 (Box 167)
  - Swainson, John B.-Michigan Governer-Judge-Book 3 K -- S 1957-1976 (Box 167)
  - Swainson, John B.-Michigan Governer-Judge-Book 4 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1959-1982 (Box 167)
  - Taft, Robert A.-Politician-Book 1 A-P, 1943-1972 (Box 167)
  - Taft, Robert A.-Politician-Book 2-P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1936-1971 (Box 168)
  - Taft, William Howard-President-B-T, 1908-1965 (Box 168)
  - Thieu, Nguyen Van-Korean Official, 1965-1978 (Box 168)
  - Thomas, Isiah-Basketball, 1990-1991 (Box 168)
  - Tito, Josip Broz-Book 1 A-R, 1944-1980 (Box 168)
  - Tito, Josip Broz-Book 2 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1943-19780 (Box 168)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 1 A-B, 1941-1972 (Box 169)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 2 B-C, 1945-1977 (Box 169)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 3 C-D, 1945-1962 (Box 169)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 4 D-F, 1944-1975 (Box 169)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 5 F-K, 1945-1972 (Box 170)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 6 L-M, 1944-1975 (Box 170)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 7 M, 1944-1976 (Box 170)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 8 N-P, 1945-1967 (Box 170)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 9 P-R, 1945-1957 (Box 171)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 10 R-S, 1938-1957 (Box 171)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 11 S, 1945-1962 (Box 171)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 12 S-V, 1944-1978 (Box 171)
  - Truman, Harry S.-President-Book 13 V-Z and Miscellaneous, 1944-1982 (Box 171)
  - United Nations-Assembly-Book 1 A-Z and Miscellaneous, 1945-1975 (Box 172)
  - United Nations-Assembly-Book 2-Miscellaneous, 1958-1982 (Box 172)
  - Van Antwerp, Eugene I.-Detroit Mayor-Book 1, 1929-1963 (Box 172)
  - Vandenberg, Arthur H.-Politician-Book 1 A-F, 1928-1963 (Box 172)
  - Vandenberg, Arthur H.-Politician-Book 2 G-S, 1926-1963 (Box 172)
  - Vandenberg, Arthur H.-Politician-Book 3 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1928-1975 (Box 173)
  - Van Wagoner, Murray D.-Michigan Politician-Book 1 A-J, 1935-1956 (Box 173)
  - Van Wagoner, Murray D.-Michigan Politician-Book 2 K-Z and Miscellaneous, 1936-1972 (Box 173)
  - Veterans-Bonus, 1932-1936 (Box 173)
  - Wallace, George-Politician-Book 1 A-P, 1965-1980 (Box 173)
  - Wallace, George-Politician-Book 2 P, 1968-1976 (Box 173)
  - Wallace, George-Politician Book 3 P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1963-1982 (Box 174)
  - Wars-World-U.S.-Army-32nd Division-Book 1, 1917-1919 (Box 174)
  - Wars-World-U.S.-Army-32nd Division-Book 2, 1918-1920 (Box 174)
  - Wars-World-U.S.-Army-339th Infantry, 1919 (Box 174)
  - Wars-World 1-Book 1, 1917-1949 (Box 174)
  - Wars-World 1-Book 2, 1916-1940 (Box 174)
  - Wars-World 1-Book 3, 1916-1944 (Box 175)
  - Wars-World 1-Book 4, 1917-1946 (Box 175)
  - Wars-World 1-Book 5, 1918-1938 (Box 175)
  - Wars-World 1-Book 6, 1917-1945 (Box 175)
  - Wars-World 1-Peace Developments, 1914-1918 (Box 175)
  - Wars-World War 2-Book 1, 1940-1947 (Box 175)
  - Washington, George-President, 1925-1982 (Box 176)
  - Williams, G. Mennen-Michigan Governor-Book 1 A -- B, 1948-1963 (Box 176)
  - Williams, G. Mennen-Michigan Governor-Book 2 C -- E, 1948-1960 (Box 176)
  - Williams, G. Mennen-Michigan Governor-Book 3 F-G, 1949-1977 (Box 176)
  - Williams, G. Mennen-Michigan Governor-Book 4 G-K, 1948-1977 (Box 177)
  - Williams, G. Mennen-Michigan Governor-Book 5 L-O, 1948-1966 (Box 177)
  - Williams, G. Mennen-Michigan Governor-Book 6 P-R, 1949-1978 (Box 177)
  - Williams, G. Mennen-Michigan Governor-Book 7 S-T, 1948-1973 (Box 177)
  - Williams, G. Mennen-Michigan Governor-Book 8 T-Z and Miscellaneous, 1949-1960 (Box 178)
  - Williams, Ted-Baseball, 1946-1982 (Box 178)
  - Wilson, Woodrow-President of United States, 1917-1979 (Box 178)
  - Woodcock, Leonard-Union Official-Book 1 A-N, 1958-1982 (Box 178)
  - Woodcock, Leonard-Union Official-Book 2 P-Z and Miscellaneous, 1948-1982 (Box 178)
  - Young, Coleman-Detroit Mayor-Book 1 A-B, 1961-1982 (Box 179)
  - Young, Coleman-Detroit Mayor-Book 2 C-D, 1973-1982 (Box 179)
  - Young, Coleman-Detroit Mayor-Book 3 E-H, 1961-1982 (Box 179)
  - Young, Coleman-Detroit Mayor-Book 4 I-M, 1969-1982 (Box 179)
  - Young, Coleman-Detroit Mayor Book 5 N-R, 1966-1982 (Box 180)
  - Young, Coleman-Detroit Mayor Book 6 S-Z and Miscellaneous, 1965-1982
Related Material
The following collections at the Bentley Historical Library may be valuable to researchers interested in the history of the Detroit News and its building. Among these are various issues of Detroit News newspapers and microfilm dating from 1912 to 1951 with some gaps in coverage.
Albert Kahn papers [includes photos and architectural drawings of the Detroit News Building]
Detroit News Lansing Bureau Scrapbooks
Isle Royale papers. (Detroit News)
The Detroit News. (newspapers) [MIRLYN catalog record]